[music]
[музыка]
blue good evening put a blasco plus sign a
синь добрый вечер поставьте бласко
little bit names and it’s okay
плюсик чуть-чуть имена и выдно нормально
yes, and
да и
we’re new
нас новыми
this board
это доска у
is new, we just go western
нас новыми просто идут одни западную
where the feed from the cell is, we introductory
куда подача от клеточки у нас вводная
go kind to the military and, in principle, cool
идут добри на военные и в принципе cool
&amp; sidney we want to quiet down the test the ointment was still
&amp; sidney хотим потише тесте мазь еще
at the front so such activity would be
была на фронте так такой активность бы
booths and you are ours you are growing and because
будками и ты наш ты растишь и потому что
you are moving and from Russian publics
ты двигаешься и от российских пабликах
you are of all kinds of kilograms our further we divide
ты всяких килограммов наши далее делим
ours passed it we were created this to the point of
наши сдал это нас создал этот до сути
whom 2 thousand of us are really like armor  the forces of
кого 2 тыс нас правде как брони силы
ukraine on the stick the swede wakes up another
украины на стике шведку просыпаются еще
pour let's say the Russians and are themselves in shock so
налить скажем россиян и сами в шоке так
let you be friends already kindness someone from the
дайте ты мог дружит уже доброта кто-то с
armor of the forces of ukraine they dig just he
брони силы украины они роют просто нему
can see the miracle is needed and so in russia
видно чудове нужен и так а в россии и
everything goes according to plan yes today Putin is there in
все идет по плану да сегодня путин там в
diamond you what is there a discount it with
даймонд вы что там скидку it with
crafting the largest damn voice in the
крафтом наибольшей чертовых голосу в
retinue
свите
probably poems astronauts sighting
наверно стихи космонавты визирование
buckets of flax this kind so you are kind to
ведра льна этот добрый так ты добр этому
this and we would have to fight for a
еще и бы нам пришлось воевать за
reasonable civilization was  pskov days
разумную цивилизация была пскова дней
staggered discounts the russian federation
шатало скидки российская федерация це
knows so well and the
така знает и
dodik power take the scenes and how 30
держава [__] возмите сцены и как 30
years grew there find all
рокив там выращивала найди все
managerial practice so you
управленческие бы практике так ты ведь
can see there it began to touch the turn to the
видно там стало касаться крути на
vertical and drip noisy you can ukraine
вертикаль и капаем шумный можешь украина
in 2014 lessons before banished yanukovych
в 2014 уроки до прогнала януковича
tayaki special red way  the Russian vertical fell to the
тайяки особые красный путь упал
group, well, it
российскую вертикаль группе ну так по
throws it and his escort goes out there
метает и выйти там его
where the money is, but there was a bunch of all
конвоир куда бабки но осталась куча все
that deku was Sarah quilted and what did this
такое дэку была сара стеганым а чем это
husband Ukraine remove the smaller path Ukraine
муж украина убрало меньшей шлях украина
wants to be in a civilized wedge and
хочет будут в цивилизованными клином и
retinue and you want Mordor and dragged into your
свиту а мордор хочешь и затянуты в свою
black hole alavann  and they live for centuries in
черную дыру alavann и мне живут веками
their clear light of the DVF, they may not be
своему явному свете двф они могут не их
afraid of their black-sea style, they are afraid of aliya rality it
стилю блэк си боятся алия ральность
seemed it’s not so yes yes I today in
показалось это не так да да я сегодня
places mmm it seems the rally for the boys is
местах ммм кажется ралли за мальчиками
just stigmata centrally 8 didn’t throw off and
просто stigmata центрально 8 не скинул и
before the stream also in May there yes konashenkov
перед стримом тоже маем там да
golovy and but the
головатого и но
press  -Secretary of the Russian Ministry of Defense, the Russian
пресс-секретарь минобороны российскую
speaker was taken away from Kharkov and the
рассказывающего из харькова забрали и
troops in order to increase pressure  they have an
войска для того чтобы усилить нажим
icon on the Donetsk front crucian carp
икону на донецком фронте караси
shown by the director Belinsky and whether you are a
показанный директор белинский и ли ты
test quarter and neighing put a
тест квартал и ржут поставьте плюсик
plus sign taba cleanly and
таба чисто а
minus the tone of his
минус тон его чи
chi can I show you for trying to show.
можна раз покажу за попробую показать .
it was at the same time on the dark canons I will
это за раз был на темная каноны буду
show it on the air of the demonstration
показывать в эфире демонстрации потому
because maybe there the brush will turn out to be an
что может там и кисть идти получится
infection of growth we won’t show for a second
зараза роста не покажем секундочку будто
if you can copyright and letters
будут можешь авторские права и писем
were from the phone in 1 moment
было с телефона за 1 момент adye
with a lever and I’ll throw a gram 100
как рычагом а я закину светили грамм 100
grams I found a canal so that everything is
грамм нашел канальчика так чтобы все
tightened and
поджал и
it can
может его
pretend to be a
прикинуться видосик
vidosik kilogram our canal so it
килограмм канальчик наш так так то там
can
может
just neigh
просто поржать
friends big about God among the Ukrainians of the
друзья большое о божьей у украинцев
savannah so midi guilty we just
саванны так миди виноватыми мы просто
like they will be released yet you will
типа их будет выпустить еще ты будешь
laugh the whole
смеяться целый
good evening lara dima besides going for a
доброго вечера лара дима помимо хожу на
month and even mashkovich on the video of the hood to
месяц и даже машкович на видео капюшона
our warriors our hero you could see
нашим воинам нашим героем ты мог видим
to japan and pan.md it will send a slave
до японии и pan.md это направит раба
for the sake of you something we here we mean
ради ты чему-то мы сюда мы разумеем
something
что-то
right on the diet puff and henry there ours
прямо на диете затяжку и генри там наши
soldiers of the sounding board and are we on you not termo you
солдаты деки а ли мы по вы не termo ты
morally plan why the help of the conversation itself
морально план почему помощи самой беседу
mutlu and the thief are such we are like cilia with a
mutlu и вора таковы мы по чем реснички с
swollen slurp  we are
заплывшему хлебалом мы таким и такте
gradually winding up the shark of guilt battery
постепенно сматываю акула вины battery
talking head greenhouse pancake
говорящая голова теплица блин
grafted with money service carpathian flour in the
привит with money service карпат муки в
carpathians cool
карпатах прикольного
views playing words hero defender of
виды играли слова героем защитником
ukraine
украины
so so and david day 2 grams until the evening
так так а дэвида сутки 2 грамм до вечера
from finland andriaki kilogram channels
с финляндии андрияки килограмм каналы
just mania bike accounts whom i
просто мания байковые аккаунты кого я
allowance for  all sorts of spam channels on there
припуск на всякие спам каналы на там
pieces 20 30 and the fact that the gecko has and
штук 20 30 а то что у геккона и
sealed ok let's start,
запечатанный ok давайте почином мог бы
maybe today garnett cinema released by
раз сегодня гарнетт кино выпущенном
chatroulette will start to get so start
chatroulette начнут достала так почином
and the axis will be like this
и ось такие буда
come on
давай
from ukraine and
из украины а
h light up russia and the
ч светиться россия а
advertist's butt was
звидки рекламиста
allowed in bukhara
обухе допускалось в бухаре
let's put it on  3 likes
давай поставлю 3 likes
take a picture of the
сфоткай
rocket tractor with it
ракеты трактор с ним
right your front is so small that
правильно ваш такий фронт маленький что
maybe it’s a robot yes I clans 6 baths at a
может это робота да я кланы 6 ванны за
time for such impudent and
раз на такие дерзкие да и
people
люди
who do you what you want i my
поможем посту кого ты что хочешь я свой
clan can chef
клан может шеф-повар
this not .  let's know, and here I came to the
этого не . давай знаешь и я вот и
great class to put down the pole
великому классе шестом проставиться
came that with 1000 you will finish with so
пришел что с 1000 закончишь с так
well yes, but the motto you encounter
хорошо да а вот девиз ты столкуешься
Ukrainian
украинскую
dsdt with boredom became Kalinin's
dsdt со скукой стал калининской
blackest Russian brought up
чернейшей российского воспитывалась
Trushkin these inserts of Donetsk just
трушкин эти вставки донецкого просто
torture turkeys come to Ukrainian
пытают индейки приходят на украинские
come on so that I tormented secrets  food
давай так у чтобы я тайны мучил питания
can indulge in the appearance of aniche as a messenger
может предайтесь вид аничей посланником
for dachas with a brain stroke, we are
для дачам с brain инсульта у нас
faster for everyone, I
быстрее всем я
hope
надеюсь
she let's fences a Pepsi-Cola bank a little
она давайте заборы банка пепси-колы чуть
bit higher than 5 so that it can be seen so
чуть выше 5 чтобы было видно так
come on mom nadia and sister ksenia you
давай мама нади и сестра ксюша вам
vitalia and the look of your brother's son and the look of andrey
виталия и вид сына брата и вид андрея
spider have a good time  cool you
паука отрывайтесь дуже прикольный у вас
clap the same screw for 6th grade such tales
хлопать таки винт на 6 класс такие байки
daring
дерзкий
outgrowths with the right language
выросты с правильным языком
here
здесь
and now I’m the
и сейчас я
regulations and
регламент и
put the same Bachili I love cool and
кладу ж таки бачили я обожаю cool и у
people are alive about the quote you accrued on the dates
людей живьем о цитата вы на даты
so you look like this icon
начислила так вы на вид эта икона
obovyazkovo goal video you put akram
обовязково цель ролик вы кладу акрама
replacement ukraine on the help channel there are more
замену украину на канал помощи там есть
important doctors go after the roll  Ika
дуже важливо врачи идти я после ролика
said so I want to install it
говорил так я хочу чтобы установить его
on the stream so by timka we will redeem the
на стриме так по тимка мы выкупим
scoundrel of
подлеца
fiction loop sweeping slam we
выдумки петля размашистым хлопнуть можем
can sound the theme of shadows often charge I’m
на зазвучат тема теней часто заряжают я
with us I think I’m reasonable
при нами я так думаешь я разумники
meeting there mountains and I would like to convey to
встречи там горы и хотел бы донести до
you
вас
andrey stream in Ukrainian will be mine
андрей стрим на украинском будет мои
comments will be ladies commentary will be
комментарии буду дамы комментарий будет
in Ukrainian
на украинском на
so wildly learning I will come the queen of synapses
так дико обучаясь приду queen синапсов
Russian Russians children are already choosing
российскую россиянам дети уже выбираем
this summer bombings the bomb of the USSR from 5
этим летом бомбежек бомба ссср от 5
all sorts of us start-up Les Gaevsky are happy
всякие нами стартап лес гаевский за рады
if we take them from to the end
если мы будем брать из до конца
to mine them glory to Ukraine okay so
добывать их слава украине окей так сам
I myself will be wild tests  until I let you go here in
буду дикие испытания до отпущу сюда в
chats if someone has these questions
чатах если у кого то есть это вопросы
there for from other countries, you can also
там по из других стран нужно тоже можете
write children we will answer them as we
писать чад будем отвечать на них по мере
find and
нахождения и
sara we agree Ukrainian armor forces
сара соглашаемся украинских брони силы
stream will simply go to Kharkiv region
стрим попросту вается на харьковщине
Rusnya resentment of the mushroom it just
[__] обиды гриба it просто на ему
returned the Crimea to him let's say  so Rusnya on and 2
вернул крым скажем так [__] на и 2
corners of the celebration of soft and good will x
уголочка торжества софт и доброй воли x
is but after all gestures of good will
является но ведь жесты доброй воли
so he is
так что он
in  from such a situation, let's
вот такая ситуация давайте поднимемся
rise one more, too, these Kaluga meetings,
еще одно тоже эти калугу встреч
let the
пусть
glory of Ukraine brother good afternoon,
слава украине брата добрый день на я из
I stuck the city of Minsk from Ukraine, I am
украины город минске воткнула я на
currently
данный момент
in Germany as a refugee, and so
про бываю в германии как беженец а так
from whether it’s a Ukrainian miracle, one
из будь то чудом украинском может один
harm can and I again rocky live  ukraine itself
вред и я опять рокки в живу украины сам
i came by nationality i am gagauz
я приехал сам по национальности я гагауз
from moldova through odessa region
из молдовы через одесской области
young moldova here zara in germany
молодого молдова вот zara в германии
dilute ukrainian mova rent
разбавляю украинскую мову аренда дуже
duze garno super
гарно супер
essence is not broken
суть не сломан
soros let’s slam with the knowledge
сорос давайте с ведома
itself from moldova windows
хлопать сам из молдовы windows
came with be to we taken out 5 rocky already
приехал с быть к мы вынутом 5 рокки уже
in ukraine  at once, a bunch of wines at a time, not
в украине зараз вин кучей же в за раз не
only five rocky, where did you make
только пять рокки где ты нажила украине
it in Ukraine, you can formulate it in Ukrainian
его на можно формулировать и украинской
language, but those who live here and don’t understand the
мовы а ти хто тут живут и не понимает
Russian-speaking jaw have been living here for 30 years and the
русскоязычная челюсть 30 лет тут живут и
problems are no longer understood by
и больше не понимаются проблемы
principles, so Kozhin can also speak
принципами так еще кожин можно говорит и
Ukrainian
украинской
run it here
запустить это здесь пропало у
[music]
[музыка]
tsar lost it, it turned on got confused,
царя это включил запутался
maybe one harm and I again rocky
может один вред и я опять рокки
having passed by nationality Gagauz
проехав по национальности гагауз
m  moldovy through the odessa region of the young
молдовы через одесской области молодого
magician
мага
zara in germany roam the ukrainian mova
zara в германии разгуляй украинская мова
linda duze garno super yes it means the essence is on
линда дуже гарно супер да значит суть на
with you she rented schools from food link
с тобой она проката школ из пищи ссылку
in the all-russian 220 hands in that switched
во всероссийской 220 руки в тому перешел
to ukrainian and into the hand and i had to go to zion
на украинскую и в руку и я к сиону
and nothing scary russians and  on
пришлось и ничего страшно россиян и на
our own, the same jellyfish is
своему и та же медуза
just so memorable for us, it
просто нам для нас на так памятна она
was listed vertically, but you’re alive to Moldova, a
значилась vertical а вот ты жив молдове
load like alots in their what Ukrainian
груз как алотты в их чего украинскому
melancholy kirovka in what’s alive and
тоски кировке в чем у жив и
again rocky, though rocky this
опять рокки хоть и рокки этот всех
shot of all so that you normally
выстрел для того чтобы ты нормально
mind and  you’re talking normally, but these
разуме и нормально говоришь а вон и эти
russians are not Ivan’s principle and you want
russian его не принцип иван и хочешь
numerical ones, and you know the hellish
численных причем во знаешь и сам адского
baths yourself, the peoples there, so yourself there, here are the
ванны си народы там так сама там вот
jokes in them there were this ashes about the
анекдоты в них был этом прах леев про
Moldavians about the Chukchi Armenians and Georgians and all of them
молдаван про чукчей армян и грузин и них
are ammonites like normal in us
всепони аммониты типа нормальным в нас
Ukrainians like us in Sony this and about
украинцев як нас в sony этот и про
Russians, too, there’s no food at a time, we know
русских тоже нету за раз еду в мы знаем
it, I’ll show it here, the Brodyan Union is victorious,
его покажу вот бродянский союз победный
then I’ll follow me to you to the bull and
буду тогда я по me to you to the bull и
we wouldn’t have all the veins arose  so alla
мы не бы все жилы возникли не так алла
jokes everyone will be there other nonsense and
анекдоты все будут там другие чушь и
at home Moldovans Moldovans 3 there are four
доме молдаванам молдаван 3 там четверо
to turn on the light bulb and you go on he’s
чтобы закрутить лампочку и ты дальше он
any fool
всяко дурня
from and the
от и
pen I can know how it turns out
ручку могу знаешь как оно получается бы
Shchedrovitsky Crimean yes it
щедровицкого крымская да то это
turns out I’m in Russian
получается я на русском а
well put plus who is in the hall  knows without
ну поставьте плюс кто в зале знает без
Georgia even a woodhouse so
находится грузия даже вудхаус так
put it plus who even understands where
поставьте плюс кто вообще понимает где
the Gagauzians live where the Gagauzians are
живут гагаузы где находится гагаузии
both just ashamed someone could not
оба просто стыдно кто-то не могли в
put the protocol on in Poland?
польше почулы протокол на поставьте ?
if you first heard about the Gagauzians about
если вы впервые услышали про гагаузов о
if today’s stream is for wild topics, you
если сегодняшний стрим за дикие тёма вы
guys know about Bogotá, but it
хлопцы мы знаем о боготу но
turns out how it is in fact the same
получается как это по факту те же самые
Turks like me Azerbaijanis when the
турки как я азербайджанцы когда была
Ottoman Empire was, that is, they fled to the
османская империя то есть они бежали на
territory of Moldova and settled there, it
территорию молдовы и обосновались там
turns out I don’t have days  it seems that it’s me
получается дни мне не кажется что это я
right now, it’s just kind of gaga for it’s not like the
щас просто вроде gaga за это не как
Turks, because the Turks were
турки потому что турки это были
Seljuk Turks, but like Crimean Tatars vodka,
турки-сельджуки а как водка крымские
no, these glass swings, it’s now
нет вот эти стеклянные качели она сейчас
I’m just wondering,
я просто меня еще интересно стало
but it became the capital of your region, this is a
но он стали столица ваше региона это
comrade if not hr  it’s necessary, comrade, yes,
камрад если не hr надо камрад да
well, how did we explain the history to us at school, you
ну как мы как нам школе объясняли вы к
studied the history of the Turks, it turns out that
нам историю изучали турки получается у
we even have similar languages other languages, but it’s not that no
нас даже языки похожи иные языки да там
all Turkic and Crimean Tat
не в том что не все тюркские и
r are also similar to me, it [mus
крымско-татарский тоже похожее на
c] is
меня-то он
lso intere
[музыка]
ting to us  a small amount of data will be needed there
тоже интересно нам нужен будет там
, laziness and
небольшое количество данных лень и
therefore little is known about you, yes,
поэтому про вас мало знают обычаю да да
yes, it
так-то
’s written that in peki peki writes about the
вот пишет что в пеки пеки пишет о
origin of the year for there are
происхождении году за существует
many different hypo  tez means the
множество различных гипотез значит
first thing is that the ancestors of the Gagauz are the
первое что предками гагаузов есть
Turkic-speaking peoples of the Oghuz Pechenegs
тюркоязычные народы огузы печенеги куман
Kuman and 2 times in Turkey, forgive us and jugs to the
и 2 в турции раз прости нас и jugs к
theory that they are the descendants of the Kunda tour,
теория то что они потомки туры кунда вот
this one that you told it even understood
эту которые ты рассказал это понял даже
there are a few there are still only
есть несколько там еще еще есть только
boo mountains on which everyone knows
бу горы на котором каждый знает свое к
as I understand it, you are Christians up to
новые я так понимаю вы христиане так до
1000 mouths, but they will cross incorrectly, you just
1000 рот но скрестят неверно просто
know, as if
знаете вот как бы
you were not on the map, and that is, you have a
на карте вас как бы нету а то есть вы
small amount of these
небольшое количество осталось вот этих
cargoes left in Ukraine in the Odessa region
грузов в украине в одесской области знаю
how
потому как
does cinema
тут кино
from Germany also live here there are many
с германии тоже проживает есть много
Russian-speaking people, like many have already
русскоязычных людей типа с многими уже
met, but Pasha at home is bored, you need to
познакомился но паша дома скучно надо
at least do something when he asks,
что-нибудь хотя бы делать при спрашивает
but by nationality, in general, Ukrainian, and
а по национальности вообще украинец а
if I go deep like that, then I’m gagauz who are who
если так углубляться то я gagauz кто кто
, what is it
такие то что такое
and
и
therefore it turns out  here it’s also when it
поэтому получается тут это также когда
’s about Ukraine before there all the former
вот про украину раньше там все бывший
Soviet calculation all Russian Russian
советский расчета все русские русские
Russians
русские
if you think so was Kievan Rus and
если так считать была киевская русь и
Russian r  Vs is low, it should be Russia,
русская русь низкая должна она россии
if you look at it like that, you can say that it
если так смотреть ее можно сказать что
doesn’t exist, see the fact that they
не существует смотри дело в том что они
meant to be called Russian Russian
значили называться россии русскими уже
much later before that there was the
намного позже до этого там было
Moscow principality, the Moscow kingdom
московское княжество московское царство
and then they hop Russia, and Russia it
а потом они хоп русь причем русь это
was, but these territories, otherwise  what
было но вот этих территориях а то что
was in the north, it was a colony, this is
было на севере это была колонией это все
all that Buryatia is now for, for example,
на что сейчас бурятии так например
they sent them a governor from earlier, the prince
прислали им губернатор от раньше князь
came there, they collect tribute
приезжал там дань собирают
from Moscow, for example, they put a
из москве вот например поставили
governor in Buryatia, they admitted it, but they
губернатора в бурятии допустил но они
need to understand they need to say, Russians they were
понять им нужно скажем вот русские они
brought up on such an imperial they need
воспитаны на такой имперской им нужно
what  then they can’t villa what they want
какой то вильи чем они хотят они не
, and
могут и
now in Germany you see
вот сейчас вот в германии ты видишь
what a difference there is between the post-Soviet
какая разница между постсоветским вот
space of ours and the European one,
этим нашим пространством и европейским
so the difference is big, yes, but they
так разница большая большая да но они
don’t want to understand, they don’t want us all to
понять они не хотят чтобы мы все эти
go there, they want everything in the world to
пошли туда они хотят чтобы все в мире
be  such [ __ ] as they have, and by the
было такое гавно как у них а
way, now Germany, here people from
кстати сейчас германии вот людям из
Ukraine, refugees don’t belong here, porridge,
украины беженцам относятся не тут кашу
here’s a couple of arrivals  or
вот пара приезжали
if you look there is in the town it turns out
если смотреть есть в городке получается
16 I can do it I’m on the land of
16 иметь у меня получатся я на земле
Baden-Württemberg,
баден-вюртемберг
it’s closer to France and Switzerland, the border and
это ближе франции и швейцарии граница и
that’s it in the town where I live here,
вот именно в городке где я живу здесь
80 85 percent of Russian-speaking
процентов на 80 85 русскоязычных
Russian speakers somehow happened
русскоговорящих как-то получилось
because when during World War II
потому что когда во время второй мировой
of the war,
войны
a lot of Russians remained to live on
очень много русских осталось жить на
this land and continued their mouth,
этой земле и продолжали свой рот
so it turns out here there are a lot of
вот она получается здесь очень много
how many people in this city, well, you
сколько население этого города ну ты
can 2025 is also a small town, that
сможешь 2025 тоже небольшой городок то
is, everything is at hand, well, as
есть все под рукой рукой подать ну как
they say, and
говорится и
maybe 40 percent for Russia, here for
процентов может 40 за россию здесь за
Russia they are  natives, and when you
россию они выходцы , да и когда ты
met from Ukraine and not a poet
познакомился с украины а не поэтом
, they start back and forth with a shot back and forth that
начинают туда-сюда шотом туда что кейсом
they took it with a case, they
забрали то забрали
might have seen it, yes, this Internet is a
может видели да вот этот интернете
joke, how this Putin asks this of his
прикол есть как этот путину этого своего
own in the hall, you
спрашивает главнокомандующий в зале надо
just need to
только
throw black well all the good
кинул black хорошо все хорошие тем
mood to run around
настроение побегать свои грузы из
glory to the heroes from the lake to
озера украине героям слава вот такие
ukraine  we don’t know yet, we don’t
про внедрить искитим мы еще не знаем
know right now, I’ll
навколо сам тут я туда
give a lot of people there, they don’t know, but
даст багато людей не знают а кто-то
let’s get to know someone in detail
давайте мы туди познакомимся детально
friendship is ready for the table, a sign of food like
дружба готов к столу знак питания типа
attacked in Poland a little browser and
нападали в польше чуть браузер и
domineering so for rastan axis
властная так за растан ось
fashion years
мода годы
in
в
live their thousand match  150000 moldova in
живут их тысяч матче 150000 молдове в
ukraine is close to 30 thousand thirty thousand in
украине близко 30 тысяч тридцать тысяч в
russia and so on it came to those
россии и так далее дальше пришло к
who know everything close 250 thousand two hundred and
знающим все близко 250 тысяч двести
forty thousand is not that brother in on the territory of
сорока тысяч не что брат в на территории
moldova here I
молдовы вот я регион
live in a compact region tested devin where
компактно проживает тестировал девин где
it is called stew from to autonomy they do
это называется рагу из к автономия у них
n’t know  for fans the status of may in moldova
не знаете фанатам статус мая в молдове
alla paid compact places of residence
алла платные компактные места проживания
and in ukraine cars of
и в украине тачки
officials where and the region is so close and
официалов куда и области так близко и
that brother p salon in ukraine for that
что брат р салоне в украине на то
simple number in the podol region
просто числе на подольской области
such a color scheme wear interspersed Russian
таким колер носите вкрапления русских
forces interspersed with the bulgarians almost in the
сил перемешку с болгаров почти в
odessa region so apples and  technical
одесской области так яблоки и техничных
bulgarian salt how are you
болгарских посолить как там у вас
quietly kind of dachshund
тихо рода такса
st story cucine tribes and tibul ivan and
st повести cucine племена и тибул иван и
paired turks loaded just  leaving
спаренными тюркам грузом просто уходом
under this
под этим
yes andersen to the Turks Serdyuk to you so and here
да андерсен туркам сердюк вам так и вот
you are on this for you came out of these step and
вы на этом за вышел из этих степа а
levan and did not accept Christianity so here is the
леван и не приняли христианство так тут
pick of lightning the peoples of alavann and Christians
кирка молнии народы alavann и христиан
so let's see it for
так давайте по вид повидай она за
food and like we fought teams so
питанием и типа нас боролись команды так
so for a second
так на секунду
he’s so strong what are the benefits of
он же они так сильно что такое блага
growth and what kind of interview to record
растичини каких бы записать интервью
I know I think giblets 2 sim the volume of
знаю я думаю потрошки 2 sim объемы
supplies for the test shafts with the captain and
поставок по тесту валы с капитаном и
gave the pedan so there will be a kremenchug and a
дали педан так появится кременчуг а и по
Kupyansk manure thrower but the blow I’m already the
метатель купянск навоз но удар я уже
source of the stocks let me kind of stay at me
исходнику запасов дайте вида stay at me
that  there to buy our kupyansk on I will
что там купить нашу купянск на буду
correctly sag balakley directly from the
правильно провис балаклеи прямо это из
beams on these balakley so ismail khan
балок на эти балаклея так исмаил хан
andrey duzhe vitalin to escape and over the
андрей дуже виталина сбежать и над
radiant ukraine a whole beautiful
осиянный украины целая прекрасную
dudamel ukrainian mova ismail khan
дудамель украинскую мову исмаил хан тебе
great respect to you that you
большой респект что ты
are trying to write to us in
изложение к нам пробуешь писать по
ukrainian there is no translator  this is
украински там с переводчиком нет это
very interesting, let's say a big big
очень интересно скажем большой большой
respect, so great was both the porridge on and the
респект так велики был и каша на и пво
air defense mariten brazenly plane trees above breathe slowly
маритен нагло чинар выше дышать медленно
wars I am lat  yshsky already understand almost everything,
войны я латышский уже практически все
that is, you stay in and koumiss of
понимаю то есть пребываете в и кумыс
labor is very fashionable, he has them 4cx go
труда очень модном у него их 4cx иди ты
damn where are you for three or four rocky tormented
блин где ты за три-четыре рокки мучаются
in Ukraine, in order to
питанием оси роблять в украине чтобы
ensure the prospects of a non-Ukrainian
обеспечить перспектив же не украинской
language, they will not yet be an expert Alexander
мовы будут пока не знатока александр
Frank above and the FRG knows who the Gagauzes were
франк выше и фрг знает кто такие гагаузы
with me Arnaut served
со мной служил арнаут
them that I am filled with
их что я наполняюсь
Arnold and the prices of this year to bask alban
арнольд и цены году этот греться alban
ti2 this at a time we polish
ti2 это за раз мы полируем
outwardly whom the water of the shadow has become bull  it’s
внешне кого стала вот вода тени bull это
so little Arnautian with them, that is, the
так мало арнаутская с их то есть
supply splashes
поставка плещется
tank gums now edema in the creatures
десну танковую сейчас отеки в твари
ilfa petrova what were you there
ильфа петрова че ты там было
[music]
[музыка]
before the
до
experienced alban
бывалый alban
ambulance there is a pressing shop alban
амбула есть прессования цех албан
angry with luck well about me often so
сердись на удачи ну про мной часто так
badly the tag figure is called there little or
плохо тэгу цифра называется там мало or
nautica
nautica
arnau  tc small and large Arnaut Yes, you
арнау tc малая и большая арнаутская да
can see the tonality was a brush Albanians
видно тональность было кисть албанцы
oh damn [ __ ] you I am for the former from donata I
ой блин [__] ты я за бывшего с донаты я
yan from when in that form that by  neither
ян из когда в той форме той пони наталья
natalia is even dyakaya and deceived, they strive to
дуже дякую да и обманула стремятся
send must i notice to the year, but
посылали must i notice году а присылает
he also sends them as far as who is Peter and mine, so
им тоже докуда кто петр и мой вот и
someone wants and Peter the hotel
кто-то хочет и петром отель
channel is overgrown so the axis can be donated
канал зарос так ось можно с донатом
so cunningly from there will be forever, as it were,
таким хитрым от будут уже вечно как бы
interrogation over here  it’s true, because
допроса над вот же нас правдина ведь у
we’re not so rich about our Ukraine, we’ll
нас мы про свою украину не так богат
obviously find out for a smile, two of them
узнаем явно прокат вот к улыбку двое
just the whole map about
всего всю карту про
Georgians with interrogations now substitutions discount
грузин допросами сейчас подмены скидку
tincture territory with Bulgarians so
настойка территория с болгарами так
epic I knew that we have Bulgarian
эпоса я знал что у нас я болгарски
solana good luck all I’m in sight allus wave to chip in
солана удачей all я на виду allus волна
how compact and the
как компактно и
territory is so well, let's share
территория так ну и давайте поделимся у
we had two positive this fight to the
нас было два позитивчик эта борьба до
fur positive about one positive
меха позитивчик об одной позитивчик
choked there will be horns
подавился будут рожки
5 years old kish and sasha
5 лет киш и саша
observation
наблюдение я из города хмельницкий а вы
with the Russians,
из украины на так общаюсь с россиянами
look, he wanted to ask such a thing,
смотри он хотел спросить такую вещь
maybe you know, because we are
может вы знаете потому что у нас
hiding information from our government, you
скрывает информацию нашей власти
give me planned on the 11th, that is,
даришь я планировала 11 числа то есть
after tomorrow 11  September to hold
после завтра 11 сентября проводить
referendums on joining Russia
референдумы про присоединение к россии
there in the Kherson region, Kharkiv region, Zaporozhye,
там на херсонщине харьковщине запорожье
LPR, DPR, and something I can’t find
лнр днр и что-то я не могу нигде найти
information anywhere, our authorities are hiding
информацию наши власти это скрывает
Ukrainians, maybe you know more, I
украинские может вы больше знаете я как
just hear about it, that is, you are such a
раз об этом слышу то есть вы так
politically inactive person, what news do I need
политически не активный человек мне
then I look at us some
новости какие то смотрю нам какие-то
telegram channels on the Internet there are
telegram канальчики интернетике там
all sorts of rbk and what
всякие рбк и что такое
it is, plus who believes read
она поставьте плюс кто верит читай чудик
crank nikola the ball will be dragged by russia a little
николы мячу протащу россия мало проводят
and referendums over their occupied
и референдумы над их оккупированных
territories about joining here tomorrow is a
территориях про присоединения вот завтра
given and numbers for the exchange of all server
данность и числа по обмену всех server
is always been the ball  put a plus on
is always been the ball поставьте плюс
who believes that this dude really
кто верит что этот чувак действительно
didn’t know and never heard ask I
не знал и никогда не слышал спроси я
was going to hold referendums
собиралась проводить референдумы вот
tomorrow September 11 on the accession of
завтра 11 сентября о присоединении вот
these cropped territories and minus
этих купирован их территорий и минус
if you are gray-haired
если вы седая
these are unpleasant this issue of Ukraine has been
эти неприятен этот вопрос украины
specifically chosen yes,
специально выбрали да
that is, you are not communicating with Ukrainians  in the
то есть вы общаетесь с украинцами не в
subject of our on the coals do not prize you why I'm
теме нашего на угли не приз вы почему я
in the subject of what's going on  in Ukraine it’s a lot
в тем что происходит на украине много то
for you to say that the referendum should
чтобы вы говорите что референдум должен
be the day after tomorrow, but then he was so
быть послезавтра но тогда так смутило
embarrassed I’ll put in Russia a single voting day
его же уложу в россии единый день
I’m not mistaken so right away and on this date
не ошибаюсь так сразу да и на эту дату
on the 11th there are already two months of true tickets
на 11 число уже два месяца true билетами
or three that there will be a referendum and about
или три что будет референдум и про
joining  Russia in Sony is preparing
присоединения к россии в sony готовит
I know, as far as I know, the dates
мне известно насколько мне известно даты
of some referendum are still no, you have
каких-то референдум до сих пор нет вам
n’t known for years, it’s already known
не было известно лет это уже известно
that no, yes, but you ask about
что нет да но вы спрашиваете про 11
September 11, I tell you that September 11,
сентября я вам говорю что 11 сентября
about the referendum, September 11, I do
про референдум 11 сентября мне ничего
n’t know anything about  the fact that the referendum was
неизвестного не про то что референдуму
supposed to take place sometime in November about
должны были пройти когда-то в ноябре об
this conversation they said a couple of days ago
этом разговоре были пару дней назад
that it seems like a naiad endures I
сказали что вроде наяду переносит я
just want navi I haven’t heard of this about
просто хочу navi я такого не слышал о на
I understood everything, then I’ll run and look for someone
понял все я тогда побегу поищу кого-то
who heard because two months ago
кто слышал потому что два месяца назад
everything  we heard about the referendum and one of them is
все слышали про референдум и один из
definitely something shorter for all of them, we
точно тут чего-то короче у всех их
wash the same month that you can go to land
промываем же месяце что можно на сушу и
and you can give a blogger, but let's try there,
и блогер можно давать а давай туда
let's fast forward  with you,
попробуйте давайте перенесемся с вами на
how many 10 years ago
сколько на 10 лет назад
we are in 2012 and
мы в 2012 и
now the intrigue yak will come up with more wines at once
вот интрига як выдумает еще зараз вин
she will test until 2012 write in your
она испытает по 2012 год напишите в свою
version so he asked let's blog
версию вот он попросил давайте в блоге
we will now fast forward 10 years back to
мы сейчас перенесемся на 10 лет назад на
10 in 2012 I already have such an intrigue
10 в 2012 год меня аж интрига такая
rasperlo from the middle that now about 2012 he
расперло из середины что сейчас про 2012
will ask me write your version on the
меня спросит напишите свою версию на
presence of the shipyard shosh winxp this is me about
присутствие верфи шош winxp это я про
2012 here we will turn for 1 2012
2012 вот мы повернемся за 1 2012
snow14 I think yes tell
снег14 я думаю что да расскажи
us
повернемся навесим уроки nevian
turn around we will hang the lessons nevian turned to give
повернулся на дать
this year on what date and what month
этом году в какого числа и какого месяца
two exactly  there were
два точно были
times like
время сколько
17 to 17 yes to
17 на 17 да
dream up a little and
пофантазировать немножко и случилось
such an event happened Japan
такое событие япония
somehow
каким-то образом
let’s say by military means
допустим военным путем у
Russia
россии
annexes those islands that
присоединяет к себе те острова которые
it considers its own, in my opinion there are three or
она считает своими это по моему три или
four islands there Kunashir and Iturup
четыре острова там кунашир и итуруп
Shikotan I don’t remember several
шикотан я не помню там несколько
islands there  but you understand what I’m saying, yes,
островов но и понимаете чем я говорю да
yes
да
, such an event actually happened and,
собственно произошло такое событие и
accordingly, I have a question, what do you
соответственно у меня вопрос как вы
think, how would the world community
думаете как бы мировое сообщество
relate  I think that the
отнеслось к этому событию я думаю это
world community would react to this event as the
мировое сообщество отнеслось бы как
return of their territories, because
возвращение своих территорий потому что
these territories legally belong to
эти территории юридически принадлежат
Japan, who do you
японии у вас
have, why is it considered so if you
кто так почему так считается если вы
think so, Japan thinks there, communicating
считаете так считает япония там общаясь
well, look at these islands
хорошо смотрите эти эти острова
belonged to Japan on the basis of what
принадлежали японии на основании какого
on the basis of what  of the peace treaty, they
на основании какого мирного договора они
moved to the territory of Russia, you can
перешли к территории россии можете
download it, no, I can’t tell you, but I
скачав нет я вам сказать не могу но я
founded a different degree again, the boy of the
основал не такой градус еще раз мальчик
world court, we look again, I want to
мировой суд одни смотрим еще раз я хочу
consider,
рассмотреть
for example, Ukraine takes Crimea back,
например украина забирает крым назад
liberates it, so Crimea belongs to Ukraine
освобождает так крым принадлежит украине
legally and it actually takes the
юридический и она его забирает
islands  about which you
фактически острова про который вы
spoke about uncritically belong to
говорили о некритически принадлежат
japan if if you consider it to
японии если если вы считаете бы его
lie on they do not belong to japan
лежат на они не принадлежат японии
japan considers their wedding again when
япония считает их свадьба еще раз когда
the same is good then answer me
то же самое хорошо тогда ответьте мне на
one simple question when so on what
один простой вопрос когда так в какую
date and on the basis of what document
дату и на основании какого документа
these islands  crossed over to Russia or to the
эти острова перешли россии или как
Soviet Union that  m of the Russian
советскому союзу там российской
Federation is not ready to answer you and I don’t
федерации не готов вам ответить и я не
know specific documents, so I
знаю конкретные документы вот вот я
think that they are what I don’t know them
думаю что они есть то что я их не знаю
color so don’t say eight pieces
color так значит не говорить восемь штук
you can search for them you can search
можете поискать их можете поискать
now so that you well and now no I don’t want to
сейчас чтобы вы ну и сейчас нет не хочу
I will look for them  you don’t have to look,
я их поищу обязательно вам не смотреть
look where you are, just just look
смотри куда ты просто просто смотрите
further, if we want, according to the imagination of
далее есть если мы хотим по фантазии у
people there, 10 years ago and
людей там на 10 лет назад и
dream up if he understood and so that
пофантазируйте если бы он понял и чтобы
we would be some kind of augers,
мы побыли какими-то таки было бы шнеками
so it would be, then we need to rely
так вот была бы вот надо тогда опираться
on  specific
на конкретные
legal concepts, so if we think,
юридические понятия так если мы считаем
well, let's say you think that
ну скажем вы считаете что это
these islands belong to Russia, then
принадлежат россии эти острова так то
you should consider them to be your own,
надо св считает их своими доносили
see consider here, for example, you can
смотрите считать вот например вы можете
consider that, say, the inheritance of the Queen of
считать что скажем наследство королевы
Great Britain, she belongs to you,
великобритании она принадлежит вам
consider you can do anything the truth of
считать вы можете что угодно правда из
people who believe  that they are napoleon and
люди которые считают что они наполеон и
but
но
practically ready for us these
практически готова нам этими островами
islands once again on actually
осуществляет раз еще раз на фактически
look for example you have a
смотрите например у вас есть
horde  er on and not closed in russia
ордер на и не закрыта в россии
is called ownership of the
называется право собственности на
premises, for example, your neighbor went into the square,
помещение например так на квадрат ваш
closed there and doesn’t let
сосед зашел закрылся там и не впускает
you
вас
in, in fact, he controls it, but
фактически он его контролирует но
legally it’s your property, so it’s a
юридически это ваша собственность так
matter of time how you are and in what way
вопрос времени как вы и в какой способ
you will expel him from there,
его оттуда вы выгоните равна
but
но
look
смотрите
you are a slightly wrong example
вы немножко неправильный пример потому
because you think you are
что вы считаете вы
making a citrine bullet, you
делаете пуля цитринку производится вы
say, but japan considers these
говорите вот а япония считает эти
islands to be its own, still the same as it once was,
острова своими еще тот же как и когда-то
japan will definitely come and stay if you
япония точно придет и оставались если вы
look if you say that these
смотрите если вы говорите что эти
islands are not legally
острова юридически не фактически
occupied by russia  and the legal one
оккупирован и россии а юридический
belongs to Russia, then on the basis of
принадлежат россии то на основании
what document of which international
какого документа какого международного
do you think you like you like to appeal
думаете вы любите вы любите апеллировать
to maps open google inc no no no
к картам откройте google inc нет нет нет
I really see what google whose cooled down
я реально смотрите че google чьими остыл
how what territory the yew is running
как какой территории тиса запущена
see google can draw as
смотрите google может рисовать как
you like so google play will draw
угодно так google играем нарисует
Ukrainian well for example  down draws
украинск ну например [__] рисует
ukrainian do you mean it  ok rena,
украински так ли вы это значок рена у
I just said that you are an operator and an
я просто сказал что вы оператор есть и
independent
независимый
politician google is a private company it is a
политик google это частная компания это
private company it is not there a
частная компания она не есть там
subject of international law as a
субъектом международного права как
state to this is so plus without appealing
государство к это так плюс не апеллируя
because it is drawn on google maps
потому что на google картах нарисована
all night, let's say there at the station
это всю ночь то скажем там на вокзале
something is also drawn on the railway, but
железнодорожном что-то тоже нарисован а
I think let's go for a robotic tour of the
пханган я думаю давайте за робымо таки
food shop of the Kuril Islands,
экскурс питания цех курильских островов
you can [ __ ] here Olga Zhuk above Andrey,
ты мочь [__] вот ольга жук выше андрей
with all due respect, does not agree that they
при всем уважении не согласна то что они
did not sign a peace treaty, it
не подписали мирный договор это ничего
does not mean anything to love and
не значит любить и
Kuril [ __ ] is not the Kuril Islands
курильске [__] не курильские острова
so there was a budley on the planet and the northern
так а будлеи планете был и северные
finish was wrong and imposed on Japan how to
финиш не так вон и наложил и японии как
find spots for the sake of the Omsk Union
найти пятнами ради омский союз
and then
а потом
Japan the United States and their food suit on the territory
япония сша и их своим на территории
niyak you say by the water
костюму питания нияк вы скажем у воды
about the transfer so not over the course of
про передачи так не над ходу
Russians and Russians in the
россиян и россиянок
British style are buying 2  here i lead
британском стиле закупаете 2 тут я веду
rents they told mpi cellular wing
арендует они велели mpi сотовая крыла
cook to get us on the switch [ __ ]
поваром чтобы нас на переключатель [__]
you knew no legal  picts of
ты знала никаких юридических пиктов
ownership prices for the
владения цены
transition in japan to russia
переходу в японии до россии
these Kuril data setting nemo and
этих данных курильских уставив nemo и
so it is absolutely similar since from the crimea
так абсолютно аналогично так как с крыму
they
они
kiss rome sparks and respect sharp
целуют риму искры так и уважаете острый
i.e. we speak in legal
то есть мы говорим юридическими
terms i.e. i have a
терминами то есть у меня есть я
few i am then a super lawyer but i
несколько я потом супер юрист но у меня
have  the second education is legal, I
есть второе образование юридическое я
’m operating if we say that,
вот оперирует если мы говорим что
for example, the Republic of Tyva once became
например республика тыва когда-то вошла
part of the Soviet Union, such a composition of the USSR
в состав советского союза таких состав
in the forties, that is, there is
в сороковых годах то есть есть
a ron determined from konami and the
определенный от konami рон и
question is when and on the basis of what act
вопрос когда и на основании какого акта
then the
тогда
territories that you voiced the islands
территории которые вы озвучили острова
so joined  to Russia,
так присоединились к россии
look, I understand your question, I
смотрите я понимаю ваш вопрос я на нее
could answer it because I’m
могло на него ответить так как я сейчас
not prepared for this
не подготовлен к этому
now, we pressed it, we don’t want it just the same and I don’t have
мы нажали мы не так же хотим и нет мне
outgrowths, but unpreparedness does
выростов на же неподготовленность не
n’t say that
говорит не говорит о том что таких
there are no such documents, we don’t know, but  I
документов нет вот не знаем но я до
mean, my preparedness says
смысле моя подготовленность говорит как
just that there are no such documents, yes, but we
раз что таких документов нет да но нас
have some kind of state other than
есть есть какие-то государство кроме
japan who don’t recognize smoked and
япония которые не признают курил и
part of russia I don’t know at all I wasn’t
частью россию абсолютно не знаю не
interested but does them no I don’t know
интересовался но делает их нет не знаю
you on the basis of what you are for these that they
вы на основании чего ты за эти что их
don’t exist but I googled
нет но я погуглил
take google after all when
возьмите погуглите все-таки тогда когда
these islands crossed and on what basis
эти острова перешли и на каком основании
I don’t want to
не хочу
I love  it’s not very beautiful to pass, we
я люблю сдавать не очень красиво мы
can someday with you in the country we
сможем когда-нибудь с вами в стране были
were talking about it, I like to enjoy it
нём рассказывать я люблю наслаждаться
when people google get ready get ready and
когда люди гуглят готовится готовятся и
no one really
никто не очень
streams to me, I write down
мне не стримлю я записываю
if you ask such a tricky
если вы задаете такой как бы каверзный
question, at least
вопрос вы хотя бы
why am I actually why and
почему я вообще собственно почему и
this question is for two,
вопрос этот за два
because in my opinion, personally, my
потому что на мой взгляд лично мой
opinion, I do not pretend to be, so to
взгляд я не претендую на какую ну так
speak, a great examination, it seems to me
сказать большую экспертизу мне кажется
that this one I agree with you in your
вот данный я согласен с вами в вашей
assessment that if this happens, the
оценке о том что если это произойдет
world community will say God there will be
мировое сообщество скажет бог не будет
no loud statements  Japan
каких-то громких заявлений японии не
will not be punished will not happen from the
накажут не произойдет со
side to punish Japan is its
стороны наказать японию это ее
territory.
территории .
further, I understand, well, that is
далее я понимаю ну то есть произойдет
, such a situation will happen and in my opinion
вот такая вот ситуация и на мой взгляд
it is not much different from
это не сильно чем-то отличается от того
what Russia did in relation to the
что сделала россии по отношению к
territory of Crimea, which is still small, let's
территории крыма еще маленького давайте
see, you are now confusing to understand and
смотрите вы сейчас путайте понять и
in the situation with Japan, so the Japanese have
в ситуации с японии так у японца есть
documents  to his apartment, and a Russian
документы на его квартиру а русский
drunk came and sits
пьяный пришел и сидит там
there again, let me tell you about the
еще раз еще раз давайте я расскажу о
situation with Crimea, so Ukraine has
ситуации с крымом так украина имеет
documents for an apartment, a Russian came and
документы на квартиру русский пришел и
takes this apartment on the basis of the
забирает эту квартиру на основании того
fact that it once belonged there, in short, to
что когда-то она принадлежала там короче
one of his relatives
кому-то из его родственников
but she was already there from Perry
но она была уже там у куплено перри
bought bought this gave me it seems to me
купленное такое дал мне кажется тут
you know it’s not very correct by
знаете не очень правильно путем нам с
talking to you about the
вами разговаривать о
territories with the presence of some documents
территориях наличием каких-то документах
it wasn’t she yelled there are documents that this is
это не она вопила есть документы что это
mine yes absolutely right look in the
моё да абсолютно верно смотрите в
ninety-first year an
девяносто первом году создалась
independent state was created  ukraine and the
независимое государство украина и
independent state of the russian
независимое государство российской
federation
федерации
in 1997 ukraine and the russian federation
в 97 году украина и российская федерация
signed a friendship treaty  e and
подписали договор о дружбе и
cooperation where they clearly said that they
сотрудничестве где четко сказали что не
have no territorial claims, they recognize
имеет территориальных претензий признают
and respect each other's borders, and then
и уважают границы друг друга и тогда
they suppose it is, get
они предположим это есть вот
ready to google, you can chat in
подготовьтесь погуглить можете чат на
public, that is, it turns out
публике то есть получается
independent states that
независимые государства которые
were created there in the ninety-first year,
создались там девяносто первом году
Russia and Ukraine, they even confirmed in 97
россия и украина они в 97 году даже
to the inviolability of each
подтвердили до нерушимость границ друг
other’s borders and to respect, that is, this is
друга и уважать то есть это есть
also recognition of these
признание также юридическая вот этих
borders, now Russia is talking about it, and there
границ теперь россии говорит о ней а там
Crimea is taking away on the basis of something on the
крым забирая на основании чего то на
basis of which what legal
основании чего каких юридических
documents of what law formally
документов какого права формально
occurred by the referent, this referendum
произошел референтом этот референдум
was not superfluous when it
не было не было лишнего когда он был
you can name the date, I don’t know March
можете дату название я не знаю марта 14
14, but I named and I’ll tell you 20
го года но я назвали а я вам скажу 20
contributes 26 on February 27, 14, the
вносит 26 на 27 февраля 14 года началась
occupation of Crimea by Russian troops began, it was
оккупация крыма российскими войсками
charged, they captured this parliament of Crimea
начислено захватили этот парламент крыма
, and so on,
так и так дальше
there can be no referendum at gunpoint
никакой референдум под дулами автоматов
if
не может быть если
because  that because if I come with a
потому что потому что если я прихожу с
gun and  I say you notice you still
пистолетом и говорю ты замечаешь ещё
want to start talking let's
захочет начала говорить давайте
talk about documents yes I'll tell you
поговорим по документам да я вам скажу
why a referendum cannot take place
почему не может происходить референдум
at gunpoint where it is written
под дулами автоматов где это написано
if the document or law in which you
если документ или закон в котором ты
touched let's do it if you think
задел давай давайте так если вы считаете
that if you can bring at
что если под дулами автоматов можно
gunpoint let's put a person in  also the motherland
давайте просовывай человек тоже родина
court two types of documents, let's go on the
суд два типа документы давайте на
basis of which document the
основании какого документа проводился
referendum was held in Crimea,
референдум в крыму
did you see the constitution of Crimea,
вы видели конституцию крыма открывали
did you open it if you are there what is said in the first article
если вы там что сказано в первой статье
before that Crimea is an integral part of the
до что крым есть неотъемлемой частью
state of Ukraine
государства украины
so
так
this is what it says, that is, look it
это о чем говорит то есть смотрите
turns out so
получается так
purely theoretically if you  again, the
чисто теоретически если вы снова
fundamental document, such a
основополагающим документе вот такое вот
complex word, is written that this
слово сложная написано что данная
territory or this region is
территория или данный регион является
an integral part of some
неотъемлемой частью какого-то
state, in this case,
государства такой вот в данном случае
it was probably the state of Ukraine
наверное было государство украина
written
написано
, does this mean that this well, that is
говорит ли это о том что этот ну то есть
, this territory
это государственным вот эта территория
does not have a state at all  n  and there is no chance of any
вообще не имеет никаких шансов на какое
kind she will determine the
бы то ни было сама определит еще раз еще
game once again on the basis of which he is based on
раз игру на основании чего он основании
what document and after that you
какого документа так и после этого вы
say that it is written in the constitution
говорите о том что вот в конституции
so I know the question is it right
написано так я знаю вопрос правильно ли
that the Crimea cannot be their residents of the Crimea
что крым не может их жители крыма нему
will be able to  they ca
смогут не могут
n’t okay okay so let’s remind you from which
хорошо ладно давайте так вы из какого
city once again and moscow moscow
города еще раз напомнить и москва москва
so for example they can decide for themselves the
так например могут а сам определится
residents of the ruble
жители рублевки
Kosinets and whom
косинец и кого
dtm and now
dtm и вот
you can self-determine the residents there,
сможете самоопределиться жители там
for example, someone in a district of Moscow
например у кого-то райончика москвы как
has access  to
на только и зависть у нас будет доступ к
you
вы
element of the dialogue of yakubov it glass and
элемент диалогу якубов него стекл и
whatman paper and
ватман и
russian easter you can evaluate we can be
russian easter ты можно оценить мы можно
yards, and up to the criterion so so here you
ярдов , а до критерий так поэтому вот вы
mean his son can be from inna can directed criterion in the head I so want it means you can from them you don’t want
хочу значит можно от их не хочешь
significant you can all advaita  we succumb
значительный можно all адвайты поддаемся
like a pro to logic and every time a brother and for
как профи логика и все раз брата и на
details an example
детали примером
can the inhabitants of the ruble
могут ли определиться жители рублевки
probably not dangerous, but you know why,
наверное нет опасной а знаете почему
because here  residents, for example, here
потому что вот жители например здесь
it’s important
важно
mass, well, not mass, but how to say
масса ну не масса а как бы так сказать
in terms of culture, the volume and these same
по культуре объем и вот этих вот самых
inhabitants, yes, you can talk about
жителей да так можно говорить про все
anything you like, they
что угодно
practice that’s it, yes, yes, where is
практикует вот вот вот именно да да где
Hegel, where are we the victims, the border
гегелю где вот это мы жертвы граница
when you can determine on the ruble
когда можно определять на рублевке
how many people live there a
сколько населения живёт там
little well, for example, in Khimki, how many people
немного хорошо например в химках сколько
live in the
живет население
lower classes, let there be a million people, I’m here a
низами пусть будет миллион человек я вот
million people, so
миллион человек так
I’ll take to prison somewhere around
я приму в тюрьму где то приблизительно
a million and a half or how much it
там миллион полтора или сколько
turns out, can the inhabitants of Khimki
получается могут ли жители химок
self
самоопределиться
-determine self-determine what you have,
самоопределиться что вы иметь
we are looking for a vat, yes, for example, they  they want to
мы ищем чане да например они хотят
proclaim a sovereign state him
провозгласить суверенное государство him
so Khimki People's Republic or
so химчан ская народная республика или
join America, for example,
присоединиться к америке например
probably in a series, but why am I in theory, yes,
наверно в череду а почему я в теории да
that is, it turns out
то есть получается
after how this state will
после как это государство будет
exist, it’s not clear, this is separate, not
существовать не понятно это отдельную не
that is, we get that the inhabitants of Khimki
то есть мы получается что жители химок
can declare independence, but I
могут провозгласить независимость но я
I don't know for sure, but it seems to me from a
точно не знаю но мне кажется с
legal point of view  and of view, probably
юридической точки зрения наверно этому
nothing contradicts this if the tweezers
ничего не противоречит если щипчики
unite and say that we are now
объединяться и скажу что мы теперь
Kerchites,
керчане
you now we will publicly voice it and
вы сейчас мы сейчас публично озвучить и
just get on the air, that is, you didn’t
просто попадет в эфир то есть у вас не
have any example, we will now publicly
было каких-то пример мы сейчас публично
voice it and that in Russia any city
озвучить и что в россии любой город
can proclaim its own  independence
может провозгласить свою независимость
from the central government, as
от центральной власти так
you know, as I don’t know specific
вы знаете как я не знаю конкретных так
norms and rules, so to speak, but it seems to me that
сказать норм и правил но мне кажется что
this doesn’t
это не чего не
contradict anything anymore, that is, it turns out that
противоречит уже не то есть получается
Khimki can declare their
химки могут провозгласить свою
independence to make their army their own
независимость делать свою армия своими
budget systems there, and
там бюджетные системы да
once again it seems to me they don’t  in this
еще раз мне кажется они не нарушат таким
way they will violate some laws, although it may be to
образом каких-то законов хотя может быть
violate the constitution, I don’t know for sure
нарушать конституцию я точно не знаю
if the constitution specifies the definition of
если в конституции указано определение
territories and how the territory is defined there,
территорий и как там определяются
it seems to me that it doesn’t rule in constitutions,
территорию мне кажется в конституциях не
but for example, a city with a population of
правит а например город с населением
50,000 people can be
50000 человек может определиться
determined again you ask me one and  the same
еще раз вы мне вы задаете один и тот же
question by increasing some by increasing
вопрос увеличивая какие-то увеличивая
I get the opposite
получаю наоборот
I want to understand I want to  for example,
я хочу понять я хочу понять например вот
Khimki can declare independence,
химки могут объявить независимость
but for example, some kind of meadow
а к примеру какой-то там как луга нам ли
there, I don’t know if anyone there, but for 50,000 it’s
кто там памяти не знаю но на 50000 это
there, tell you your region, well, I don’t
там назовите вам вашей области ну я не
know, let there be some new
знаю пусть будет какую-нибудь там новые
Khimki there 2
химки 2
why the ruble cannot declare
почему рублевка не может объявить
independence and Khimki can, but once again,
независимость а химки могут но еще раз
look, my thought was
смотрите моя мысль заключалась в том что
that this declaration of independence
вот это вот объявление независимости
is connected with a certain amount of volume to
связано с некоторым объемом объемом жить
live, somewhere in which to measure the volume it
вот где-то в чем измерить объем это
should be neither of my own 1,100,000,
должно быть ни своих 1100000 у меня нет
why do you think that in the Crimea
а почему вы тогда считаете что в крыму
there was a sufficient volume of inhabitants for this
достаточный был объем жителей для это
whole not, well, for example, it’s good to take it
целая не ну например хорошо возьмем там
for a fitting, this is the Altai Territory and the
на примерку это алтайский край и
Altai Republic, the population is not enough for you, the
республика алтай население мало вам
territory is large
территория большая
yakutia, the sea can now be a print of Yakutia,
yakutia море может сейчас принтом якутии
then the republic, let’s return to the region,
то республика давайте мы в область
that is, it turns out
вернемся то есть получается
the same, probably the Luga region,
тот же самый то наверняка лужский район
Kaluga  the region is so huge
калужская область так огромная
territory of the Crimea the
территория крыма
Kaluga region can declare
калужская область может провозгласить
independence so
независимость так
well, once again it seems to me that it would not be  it will
ну еще раз мне кажется это не будет
contradict, I’m not sure, but it
противоречить я вот не уверен но мне
seems to me that it will not contradict the
кажется это не будет противоречить
Russian address, but it will be different, I
российскому адрес да будет другим не
’m not sure why, why will you
уверен будет почему почему будет вы
say seals, because you do
скажете печатки потому что у вас ну не
n’t provide for obtaining independence
не предусмотрено получение независимости
by some regions of the cities of the republic,
какими-то областями городами республики
it is written in what law to talk to
это написано в каком законе поговорить у
we are not foreseen for a year or not
нас не предусмотрен год или а не
foreseen there is no such thing they don’t
предусмотрено нету такого они не
watch you anime you say know how
смотрите вас аниме вы говорите знать как
you are doing you don’t have any I understand I
делаете у вас нет никакой я понял я
understand ya benito let’s do it if we
понял яа бенито давайте так если мы
take the ussr so in the heart and in the
возьмем ссср так в сердце и в
constitution in the agreement on creating the goal
конституции в договоре про создания цель
was clearly spelled out  that the union
была четко прописано что союзные
republics have the right to freely secede
республики имеет право свободного выхода
from the EU so it was written in Russian
из ес так было прописано в российском
legislation that there is no such thing, that is, there are
законодательстве такого нет так то есть
no rights for these regions,
никаких прав вот этим там областям
cities about self-determination,
городам про самоопределения не указан
if indicated, tell me, I’ll tell you, I
если указано скажите мне я скажешь я
was wrong
ошибался
to talk about the constitution of the USSR and about the
говорить про конституции ссср и про
agreement on the creation of the USSR,
договор о создании ссср
well  yes, probably the creation agreement with a more
ну да наверно договора создания с более
important document at that time was than
важный документ на тот момент был чем
no constitution, look when there was an
конституцию нет смотрите когда был
agreement on the creation of the ussr, the constitution was not
договор на создание ссср конституции не
a constitution, it was already on the
было конституция она делась уже на
basis of the agreement, the
основании договора
fundamental document was another
основополагающий документ был другом
lair consciousness for the creation of an actual
логово сознание на создание фактически
state with the name of the ussr, and in this
государства с названием ссср и в этом
agreement it was written that the last
договоре было написано о том последний
bromide that the union republics have the
бромида что союзные республики имеем
right to freely exit from  ussr swap
право свободного выхода из ссср swap
union republics have the right to
союзные республики имеют право на
free exit from okay well there was
свободный выход из окей хорошо вот была
such a construction then there appeared
такая конструкция потом там появилась
constructions everything else now you
конструкции все остальное теперь вы
say that in the russian federation
говорите что в российской федерации
such an option to exit from the
такая опция выхода из год выхода из-под
jurisdiction
юрисдикции
of some area the
какой-то области
court of the subject subjects of the territory from the essence
суд субъекта субъекты территории от суть
look  about the court, you’re
смотрите про суде ты про субъекты как
not ready to say about subjects like republics,
республики так не готов сказать вот
honestly, I’m not ready, but about the region there’s definitely
честно не готов но про области точно
no such thing, it’s definitely missing, I
нету такого точно отсутствует
could
мог о
say that there are no legal
том что о том что нет юридических
grounds for the Kaluga region to secede from
оснований там калужской области выйти из
the federation, it’s time for me to be the most
состава федерации мне время мне самое
interesting from with you all-  understand
интересное от с вами все-таки понять где
where you have the counter in your head  from this level
у вас счетчик в голове вот этого уровня
how many people already then how many people
сколько человек уже тогда скольким людям
are allowed to proclaim their
разрешается провозглашать своим
independence they are not allowed to cool down
независимым остыть им не разрешается
I have no answer to this question this is a vapid
меня нет ответа на этот вопрос это vapid
question an interesting experience on if the answer to the
вопрос интересный опыт на если ответ на
deal the reviews in your head have determined
сделка отзывы у себя в голове определили
that Crimea can be self-determined but
что крыму можно самоопределиться но у
you do not have this counter in  head
вас нету этого счетчика в голове
but your idea is clear
но идея ваша понятно
I will
я
find out the answer
выясню ответ
answer
ответить
you go yes there in the chat roulette ask
вы выходите да там в чат рулетку задаете
questions there
там вопросы
I’m talking I’m not trying to travel around
разговариваю я не пытаюсь колесить
to carry you ask a question there about the
возить вы задаете вопрос там про
Kuril Islands but somehow you are
курильские острова но как он как-то вы
not prepared you need to read here
не подготовлена вам надо почитать тут
arose and what is there  well, if you
возникала а что там такого ну если вы
want to ask some such question, it
хотите задать какой-то такой вопрос вам
would be logical for you to at least read some kind of base,
бы логично было бы какую-то базу хотя бы
therefore, here I
почитать поэтому здесь понять
turned to understand from the point of view of some kind of
повернул с точки зрения какого-то такой
work on the bridge, otherwise, the uterus is prepared,
работы на мосту а то а вот подготовлена
who are the haste of these and what
матка вы кто поспешности этих какой
kind of technician  it's important, well, there is a
именно и техник это важно ну там
designer programmer, a layout designer, then
дизайнер программист верстальщик то
how much space is it than a program, it's
сколько места она чем программе это же
just a python programmer
просто программист на питоне пайтона
well cool on the hand we
хорошо прикольно на руке есть у нас
can have some last question
можете какой-то напоследок вопросик
yes I don’t know but it would be interesting
да я не знаю но было бы интересно
here is your question and you know now
вот ваш вопрос а вы знаете вот на раз уж
we are talking with you you know
мы с вами разговариваем вы сами знаете
[music]
[музыка]
music I thought to leave and said
музыка я думал оставить и наговорил
say the question
говорите вопрос
most curious if the answer is at all to
самому любопытно если ответ вообще на
this.  how this criterion is determined,
это . как вот определяется вот этот
does it exist at all or does not
критерий он вообще существует или не
exist
существует непонятно такой вопрос не сам
?  there are few
там рублевке нельзя потому что там мало
people there and in the empty pole you don’t
людей и в пустые полюс не
understand what else is that you
понимаете ещё какая штука то что вы
give an example of an example from the ruble, but this
приводит пример пример с рублевки но это
is a concrete example if you are a ruble example,
вот конкретный если вы рублевский пример
nobody needs it firstly because
это никому не надо во-первых потому что
as people will
как люди будут
they become some kind of us
они стали какими-то нами
they become
они стали
[music  ]
[музыка]
states I didn’t have them to
государства у меня это уже их не было
figure it out, it’s an interesting
разобраться интерете интересный вопрос
question, look, the Chechen Republic of
вот смотрите чеченская республика
Ichkeria so it was to dig and took off
ичкерия так было копать и снял
proclaimed its independence
провозгласила свою независимость
as to why Russia
как по через почему же россия
attacked Chechnya and wouldn’t let it if it
напала на чечню и не дала если бы она
were independent, but I don’t know the history of
была независимой но я не знаю истории
Chechnya they  not 1 and not 2 Chechen,
чечни они не 1 и не 2 чеченского ничего
I can’t say anything about this, damn it or
по этому поводу сказать не могу блин или
special operations,
спецопераций
then what is the legal concept of the
то что же юридическое понятие
semantic difference
смысловая разница
to St.  while
до свидания пока
pasta keddah vacuum
паста keddah вакуо
rolls on this about ukraine there
не катит на этом про украину там вот
Crimea could separate aspens can’t
крым мог отделяется осинки не могут
why because they are few small
почему потому что они мало мало
population in crimea a lot of icloud and try
населения в крыму много icloud и пытаюсь
and where is this we are only a little rich
а где вот это мы же лишь малое богата
between enough for you
между достаточно для вы
significantly if the answer to this  the question
значительно если ответ на этот вопрос
is, such rams in the chapters are going on in it,
вот такие овны в главах творится в нем
everyone
все
lives on a TV and the imperial
живут телевизор и имперского
Crimea had the right to separate and completely
крым имел право отделиться и вовсе
transliterate to know the IR repeater and the
транслит знать ик-ретранслятор и
market didn’t think about it
рынок не задумался у него входа
.  includes from the exchange
да что за музычка включает от обмена
in the cher boom in the video with captain qing
в чера бум в видосик с капитаном цин
bloggers just stood there automatically
блогерам так и просто стояла автоматично
shaving 1700 started then the premiere
shaving 1700 запускалась то премьера
hotel 5 such ways of the premiere starts the
отель 5 такая путей премьеры запускается
sound such types of connections weighing from the
звук такие типы подключений весом от
latitude and why yes so let’s tell the
широты и почему да так давайте поведана
food
питанием
so
так
ismail khan andrei about the situation
исмаил хан андрей по поводу ситуации
connected  with the Hong Kong Taimanim by others,
связанной с гонконгом тайманим другими
should they be recognized as
ли должны ли они признаваться в качестве
independent sovereign
независимых суверенных государственных
states?  formations vita hong kong and taiwan
образований vita гонконг и тайвань у них
they have completely delighted them and took out ukraine yes
у них совсем радовать и вынес украины да
so hong kong and taiwan have completely different
так у гонконга и тайваня совсем разной
history hong kong was a territory
истории гонконг это была территория
controlled by the uk and if I
подконтрольна и великобритания если не
’m not mistaken and the
ошибаюсь и
uk we eat gave the status of the show
великобритания едим отдала статус шоу
this territory will return to the Chinese
это территория вернется уже к китайскому
state so but with what  -something there is a
государству так но с каким-то там
transition for some years and with the
переходом сколько-то лет и с
restriction that, for example, the tunnels should be preserved there, the
ограничением что например там должен
economic system
сохраняться тоннели экономический строй
rejoices, and there something was a whale, the conditions were the
ликует а там что-то было кита условия
basis for a completely different situation with you,
основанием совсем другая ситуация с ты
it was the Chinese Republic,
его ним вот была китайская республика
and the
а
communists made a revolution there and
коммунисты сделали там революцию и
created a Chinese people's
создали там китайскую народную
the republic and the Chinese communists
республику так и китайские коммунисты
seized power and
захватили власть и
in a number of ways, like the government of China, she
у ряд как правительство китая она
fled to the island of Taiwan and, in fact,
убежала на остров тайвань и по сути
Taiwan is the same Chinese but before the
тайвань это те же самые китайцы но до
communist
коммунистические
mainland China, which is called the
материковый китай так который называется
People's Republic of
китайская народная республика
China, Taiwan is called the Republic of China,
тайвань называется китайская республика
this is the island of Taiwan, and so at least the
это остров тайвань а так хоть китайская
Republic of China
республика
mainland china e  then the People's
материковый китай это китайская народная
was, in theory, the same
это по идее было одно и то же
state, but on the territory of
государства так но на территории
mainland China, the communists seized
материкового китая коммунисты захватили
power and
власть и
this and the
этот и
government that was there, she
правительство которое там был она
fled to Taiwan and from mainland
убежала на тайвань и с материкового
China they could not take Taiwan
китая они не смогли ты-то взять тайвань
and what is most interesting if  I’m not mistaken,
и что самое интересно если я не ошибаюсь
he was the
то он
founder of
антор входили основателями как раз тот
China, which is Taiwan, and only in 70
китай который тайвань и только в 70
some year he replaced
каком-то году он заменили
that taiwan with that China with the wrong
тот taiwan на тот китай на не тот китая
China, so it’s very interesting to read about the
вот так очень интересно почитайте про
history and Taiwan the gunslinger came
историю и тайваня the gunslinger пришли
international law to take a steam bath
международное право на попарились
written  audi its on in fact 9 acres
написано audi его на по фактами 9 соток
most answer to the right to the pair
самый отвечай на право на по паре
written account will wash it right
написано счет вымоет этом право там вас
there you just don’t want to do it, but you also
на этом надо только не желает но еще у
have someone in your phone so what’s the
вас кто в крав ваш телефон так чем
car in fact taking the stubb
машину по факту линии забрав стубб
windows of the illegal ludi
windows незаконного ludi
yulya allochka means  sasha the right to
юлечка аллочке значит саша право на
sell after the fact until the phone is on and the eye is
продажу по факту пока телефон по и глаз
not so
не так
pleading i.e.  mechanisms yak sort out the
мольбу т.е. механизмы як разобраться в
unkind cost but imperiously kyzy kind you are in
недобрый стоить но властно кызы вида ты
good faith so who doesn’t jump khimki
добросовестно так кто не прыгает химки
department of khimki so let’s not
отделение химок так давайте не решаетесь
decide about itan and never here so
об итане и сюда никогда так
chicco I’ve done my time to fly and from the
chicco я наделал срок себя летать и со
hearing of such people the threads of whom
слуха таких людей нити кого
will be so
будут так
what for db
что за db
him in tube  is weak the obsessian federation
ему in tube is weak обсе ской федерации
does not have the right to withdraw from its composition, the
не обладают правом выхода из ее состава
comrade just realized that now he will
товарищ просто понял что сейчас будет
dunk and decided to hide technically from
макать и решил скрыться технично из
Andrey cheats
андрея читы транслит выдумки про
I am engaged in premium sweet this is lysh I am engaged in
где я занимаюсь в на премку sweet это
children I just enjoy the kind of
лыш занимаюсь детьми я просто кайфую вид
training for children tourism their olympiads the
подготовки детей туризм их олимпиад
program is not on film I
программа не в тему на пленку я
am engaged
занимаюсь
with an adult I let them rest
с взрослому мне пусть нонын отдыхали
absolutely also for adults no
абсолютно также для взрослых никаких
such influential mind so the dna
таких влиятельных виду так кашеварка днк
cooker celorico is granted to merge began
celorico дарован сливаться начала
by law
по закону
hammer conceived tea kaishi
молот задуманный чай кайши
taiwan like donbass 3 30 bath like
тайвань как донбасс 3 30 ванне как
donbass only in china dong  bass
донбасс только в китае донбасс
for peter i make russia and the lower powers
за петр i make россии и низшие державы
so let’s leave it open to
так ведь бросим открывается для то чтобы
see and qualitatively the territories view of
видел и качественно территорий вид
ukraine
украины
in china there will be horns to the former priest of the essence
в китае будут рожки бывшему попу сути
from that chinese woman at a time
от той китайки за раз
legal legal vlada flashlight once in
законный законно влада фонарик раз на
taiwan so only prices taiwan
тайване так только цены тайвань
separatists
сепаратисты
revolution mind affectionate mystical  in
революция виду ласковыми мистично в
mainland china so frequent on the
материковом китае так часты на
territory it means in part on the
территории значит на части на
mainland it was bought by the communists by the
материковый было закуплено коммунистам
chinese
китайскими
in taiwan saved you a statue of the currency
на тайване сберегла сь вы статуя валюте
for vlad
на влада
so the address of validity rush drive the loot
так адрес годности мчаться гони бабло
russia held which 20 beads are few
россия держала которая 20 бисеринок мало
taken on the market it is worth listening to it
взяты на рынке стоит слушать она там
will light up there the brush is still srach shorter than russia
загорится кисть таки срач короче россии
you are fireworks of Moscow Ivan and fireworks are fired
вы фианитами москвы иван и салют пускают
down people I’m still 10 grams
вниз люди я вот поки 10 граммов
kilograms channels of Russian smart yet
килограмм каналы российских умных таки
this is Moscow fireworks of equals here
это москве пускают салют равных тут
fireworks of others I’m going to we just
салют других ним иду по мы просто
give channing then already in the Luhansk region
даем ченнинге потом уже на луганщине
this and releases all the super rating of
такое а выпускает всю супер рейтинг
Putin’s heart of all sorts of even them with pepper
путина сердце всяких даже им перцем
champed and already falling they
champed и уже падает у них
shaft is the main table to the bottom  empire
вал это основный стол к нижней империи
type there is an emperor he knows everything he
типаж вот есть император он все знает он
in my opinion he fumbles in the ass you are 30 rocky in
по моему он шарит в жопу вы 30 рокки в
volodya kleptocracy to ukraine and
буду володьку клептократии на украину и
to java korotchenko the old car is so
к java коротченко старая машина так
easy to try and the fire is on track and
просто попробовано и костер на лад и
now interrupted
теперь прервал
international law on it is possible to
международное право на можно в
apply that criminal
криминальным применим ту криминальный
landing in criminal  an excess of numbers in the international on
десанте избытка чисел в международный на
twitter and a single dacha introduces the fact that
twitter и единый даче внедряет то что
tomorrow the title of the board in the international
завтра званием плате в международном
also in principle can be seen in the summer I
также принципе можно разглядеть летом
’m glad to quickly Keanu to us already but consider
рада быстро киану нам уже но считаетесь
let’s say those
скажем те
sanctions give highscreen so-and-so and dyna
санкции дайте highscreen так-то и дины
shore than to kill him not so
шор чем убить его не таким и
effective and criminal here  then I
эффективными и криминального тут тогда
caught and planted how Kaliningrad exists,
поймал и посадила как существуют
they didn’t have down Russia, and the
калининград не имели вниз россии также и
ruble of Khimki will exist so
рублевкой химки будет существовать так
they look like they’re from Kherson, Putin’s tasks are not counting the
вид они из херсона путин задачи не счет
train, this is the
поезда это
Tiksi of the abyss, the floor of the water at the junction,
тикси пучины этаж воды на стыке
sighting in ideality, so we
визирование в идеальности так то планы
lay out the plans, they died, they give reports to the
выкладываем умер у им дают отчеты
psychiatrist of the Klinsky arm length  did not include
психиатру клинском длины рук не включил
slander and kind of sex
злословит и вид секса добры все
kindness all beautiful will burn steam profitable
прекрасными выжгут steam выгодному
shining there super army super
светящими там супер армия супер
how much and so on
насколько и так далее
so it’s his nikita it’s like white and
так это его никита это как белые и
red only no one else go
красные только никто еще не по иди
person straight and sugar mama’s muffin hero into
person прямо и сахар кекс мамы витязь в
new ones suits us and silence
новые нам подходит и тишина счетам
comes to accounts there comes I’ll find like
наступает там наступает найду лайкать
information that we’ve entered the Donetsk
информации что зашли на донецкий
airport appointed  fake repairs
аэропорт назначил фейковые чинишь
effective to and removes before the court the essence of
эффективные к и снимает до суда суть
this is right there for him couleur kenzo
этого там у прямо ему couleur kenzo
Ukrainian zbroi are not strong and once again
украинские зброи не силы и еще раз
pass the push or you cheese and our
пассеруйте пуш или ты сыр и наших
Ukraine you a little api days themselves bake
украине тебе чуть api дни сами печете
joys we won’t give birth to you and sperm we won’t give birth to
радости мы по вы не родит и сперма мы по
you  cotton collection and there is half more
вы не буду ваты сбора а там еще половина
david otherwise he
дэвид иначе прекрасной servicii вертолет
will have a beautiful servicii helicopter because he has depression
будете у него ведь бывает депрессия
very much more depression I will be at the enemy
очень больше депрессии буду у ворога ты
you better wake up with him not rabble not
уж лучше у него очнуться не сброд не
disintegration not to get confused
дезинтеграции не путаться и мы при можем
our
напустить что такого места дуешься наш
stream then you are and I
стрим тогда вы находитесь а я
visualize the judges in the head so
визуализируется судьи в голове так
simply tengri you are trying to bachim
просто тенгри вы пытаетесь побачим
sincerely strive to transfer boxing and
искренне стремлюсь бокс передать и
twitter I am with  contract wars 2 and fly from
twitter я с contract wars 2 и летать из
so little run to allow you don’t have
так мало запусти to allow не обладаете
rights and for the fact that we couldn’t stock
правами и за то что не смогла мы запас а
otherwise I’ll go like this and from whether you can
то так и от буду идти ли ты можешь
believe we will record a streamer at the back without
верить мы запишем у спины стримчик без
sold hellish type baby skidan means
продан адский типа малышка скидан значит
in Cologne and straight and  suit and glory to
по кельна и прямо и масть а слава
Ukraine
украине
[music]
[музыка]